Guide to the Gligor Tashkovich papers,1983-2015.
Tashkovich, Gligor papers,1983-2015.
- SERIES V. UNITED STATES.
  - Small Enterprise Assistance Funds, July 2004 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    The Development Impact of Small and Medium Enterprises
  - Flag Day and White House World Heritage Day, June 14, 2016 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - New York State Political Mailings and catalogs, 2007 - 2017 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- SERIES VI. INTERNATIONAL COMMITTEES.
  - E-mail scams, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - African scam e-mails (see also Nigerian scam e-mails), 2002-2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Albania-Bulgaria-Macedonia Oil (AMBO), 1994-2004 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - British Information Services, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1996-2004 (Box 10, Folder 5-13)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Calendar & Chronicle, 2000-2006 (Box 10, Folder 14-18)
  - East West Institute, 2000, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - European Bank, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights in Greece, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - International Business Opportunities, Post-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - International Politics, 2001-2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Internet Society News, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 2004 Olympics (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Prince of Wales Business Leaders Forum, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - U. S. - Eastern Europe Trade, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Institute of peace, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Volunteers in Overseas Cooperative Assistance (VOCA), 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - World Culture Open, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - World Energy, 1999-2004 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Folder 1, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Folder 2, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Folder 3, 2002 - 2003 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Folder 4, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Agency for Foreign Investments of the Republic of Macedonia, 2005 - 2006 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    "Basic Concepts for Investing in Macedonia" and an FAQ pamphlet
  - AID - US-Muslim World Relations, July 8, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Balkans - International Intervention Reports, February 22, 2002 - February 26, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs - British Government; United States Institue of Peace
  - Centre for European Policy Studies, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    "A Stability Pact for the Caucasus"
  - Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe, February 17, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    "Briefing on U.S. Assistance to Central and Eastern Europe and the NIS: An Assessment"
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Folder 1, 2000 - 2005 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Folder 2, 2006 - 2016 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Eurasia Group - Turkmenistan, September 2009 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    Political risk and advisory group - includes menu, speeches, and information about Turkmenistan
  - European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1994 - 2001 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    Includes opening statements to annual meetings, a presentation about reforming polieicies in central and eastern Europe and the former Societ Union, and a regional strategy publication entitled "The Road to Stability and Properity in South Eastern Europe."
  - European Bank for Reconstruction and Development - International Financial Institutions, March 29, 2000 - March 30, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    "Regional Private Sector Initiatives in South East Europe: Stability Pact Funding Conference"
  - European Bank for Reconstruction and Development - Investor's guidebook, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    Croatia, FYR Macedonia, Slovenia
  - European Commission DG Energy and Transport, November 24, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    PAN-EUROSTAR: Pan-European Transport Corridors and Areas Status Report
  - Musiad USA World business summit, 2017 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - European Economy European Commission: Englargement Papers, December 2006 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - European Investment Bank, March 29, 2000 - March 30, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Basic infrastructure investments in South-Easten Europe: Regional Project Review - Regional funding conference for South-Eastern Europe
  - European Union - Folder 1, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Documents concerning the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia
  - European Union - Folder 2, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - European Union - Folder 3, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Documents include a 2007 progress report on Macedonia, a publication titled "Enlargement Strategy and Main Challenges 2007-2008," and an additional document conerning the Accession Partnership with Macedonia.
  - Instanbul Leadership Institute, 2015 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Macedonia Democracy Network, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Concerning a funding application to promote non-governmental organizations (NGOs)
  - Macedonia - Ministry of Environment and Physical Planning, 2006 - 2012 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Macedonian Academy of Sciences and Arts, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Macedonian Finance Government Publications, 2006 - 2007 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    In Macedonian
  - Macedonia - Tempus, February 2008 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    "Compendium of Tempus Projects with Macedonian Participation Financed in the Period 1996-2007"
  - Macedonia - UMD Global Conference, 1996 - 2010 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    Information concerning the promotion of investing in Macedonia.
  - Macedonia - United Nations Global Development Programme, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Macedonia - USAID - Folder 1, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    "Report on Foreign Trade of Macedonia"
  - Macedonia - USAID - Folder 2, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Macedonia - VMRO-DPMNE, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
    Internal Macedonian Revolutionary Organization – Democratic Party for Macedonian National Unity
  - Omam - Ministry of the National Economy - Publications, 2003 - 2007 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Contains booklets with economic data and information, information about gender equality, a copy of a privatisation law, and census data.
  - Reform of the International Monetery Fund, 2009 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    "Investment destination of municipalities in Macedonia" and "Early Warning Report Survey Results"
  - Regeringskansliet Ministry for Foreign Affairs, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    "Strategy for development cooperation with Macedonia" January 2006 - December 2010
  - Republic of Macedonia Ministry of Finance - Folder 1, 2006 - 2008 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    In English - Annual Economic Report 2006, Bulletin 2006, Bulletin 2008
  - Republic of Macedonia Ministry of Finance - Folder 2, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    In Macedonian - 2006
  - Republic of Macedonia Ministry of Finance - Folder 3, 2006 - 2007 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    In Macedonian - 2006 - 2007
  - Republic of Macedonia Ministry of Foreign Affairs, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    Macedonian Diplomatic Bulletins 2007
  - Republic of Macedonia Securities and Exchange Commission, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Samruk Kazyna, 2016 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    Comphrensive privatization plan for Kazakhstan for 2016-2020
  - Search for Common Ground, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    "Transforming Conflict Around the World"
  - Telecoms Development in Central and Eastern Europe and the Former Soviet Union - Folder 1, 1992 - 1995 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    European Bank for Reconstruction and Development
  - Telecoms Development in Central and Eastern Europe and the Former Soviet Union - Folder 2, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Trade Promotion Coordinating Committee, June 9, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    Business forum for Southeast Europe - US Department of Commerce
  - United Nations and Nexus Global Youth Summit, July 21, 2016 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - U.S.-Central Asia: Partnership for Economic Progress, May 2, 1994 - May 3, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - World Bank, 1996 - 2006 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    Document concerning a proposed first programmatic development policy loan of Euro 24.4 million to Macedonia. "For Official Use Only." Additional document titled "Key Sources of Growth" for Ohrid, Macedonia.
  - Macedonia - Folder 1, 1998 - 2007 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Diplomatic List, Ministry of Finance Bulletin, Progress in Policy Reforms, Diplomatic Bulletin,
  - Macedonia - Folder 2, 2005 - 2006 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Annual Report Foundation Open Society Institute, 2006 Economic Report, Ministry of Finance bulletin
  - Macedonia - Folder 3, 2006 - 2007 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    ODIHR, Investing in Macedonia, publication in Macedonian
  - Macedonia - Folder 4, 2001 - 2010 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Education development strategy, United States Embassy Skopje art program, speech by Polish ambassador to Macedonia, UMD voice, investing guides
  - ODIHR - Election Observation Mission: Bosnia and Herzegovina - Folder 1, September 21, 2010 - October 4, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    General Elections on October 3, 2010. ODIHR = Office for Democratic Insitutions and Human Rights. Contains a letter to Tashkovich explaining acceptance of position as a Short-Term Election Observer, along with an Interim Report from OSCE explaining the structure, concerns, and climate of the general elections. Included also is a compilation of legal documents for short-term observers, a contract for national staff, observation report forms, and other related materials.
  - ODIHR - Election Observation Mission: Bosnia and Herzegovina - Folder 2, July 2010 - October 3, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Contains manuals for polling commissions in Bosnia and Herzegovina, a logistics information booklet, a blank qualitative election observation form, rules of conduct, and a regional briefing pack.
  - ODIHR - Election Observation Mission: Bosnia and Herzegovina - Folder 3, October 3, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Contains a glossary of election terminology, an election observation handbook, and an international observer guide.
  - Various committee packets and conferences, including No Labels and ...-, 2017 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Macedonian Diplomatic Bulletin, 2014-2015 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- SERIES VII. INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS.
  - Albania, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Armenian election, 1999-2003 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Azerbaijan, 1995, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 16-23)
  - Balkans, 1993-2004 (Box 11, Folder 24-27)
  - Balkans (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Bosnia, 2001, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Bulgaria, 1994-2005 (Box 12, Folder 1-7)
  - American University in Bulgaria (AUBG), 2006 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Caspian Sea, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - China, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Croatia, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
  - East European Oil Investment, 1994-1999 (Box 12, Folder 12-16)
  - Eurasian Economic Summit,Istanbul, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Kazakhstan elections (see also international politics), 2004 (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
  - Macedonia, 1986, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - TeleCom 91: 6th World Telecommunication Exhibition and Forum, 7-15 October 1991, Geneva, Switzerland (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Macedonia, 1992-2001 (Box 13, Folder 1-8)
  - Macedonia, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 1-12)
  - Macedonia, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
  - Macedonia: homosexuality, 1999-2004 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Macedonia: Correspondence re Investment, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 16-19)
  - Macedonia: Correspondence re Investment, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 20-21)
  - Short History of Macedonia, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Macedonia, Minister for Foreign Investment: files, memorabilia, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 2-8)
  - Christian Embassy of Canada, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 9 and box)
  - Menus, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Commemorative stamps and postage, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Hotels, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 12-13)
  - Invitations and thank you notes, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Bartholomew, Archbishop of Istanbul, New Rome and Ecumenical Patriarch, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Macedonia, Minister for Foreign Investment: Christmas and New Year's cards, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Additional Macedonia files, 2006-2012 (Box 29)
  - Nigerian scam e-mails (see also African scam e-mails), 1998, 2000-2004 (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
  - Nigerian scam e-mails, 2009-2013 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Romania, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Russia, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Yugoslavia, 1989, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Misc. international material, 2009, 2013 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Macedonia travel info (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Material on 2012 Republic of Georgia Parliamentary elections, Tote bag (Box 32)
  - Misc. international material, 2013-2014 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Ukraine, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - China Institute, 2013 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - American Research Center in Sofia, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - American Research Center in Sofia, glass paper weight, 2004-2014; MU-2227 (Box 38)
  - American Research Center in Sofia, 2009-2013 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - E-mail scams, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Halo Trust, 2014-2015 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Albania - 1999 Country Profile, April 1999 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - American University in Bulgaria - Folder 1, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - American University in Bulgaria - Folder 2, 2006 - 2007 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - American University in Bulgaria - Folder 3, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Board of Trustees Meeting 2008 materials
  - "A Reader's Guide" - Albania, The Caucasus, Central Asia, Conflict in the Balkans, Bulgaria, Serbia, 1993 - 1999 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Azerbaijan International, 2004 - 2005 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Magazines
  - Bulgaria - Economy and Politics, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Contains two publications by Cornell professor Elena Iankova, and "A Brief History of the Interet."
  - Conflicts in Southeastern Europe, 1994 - 2009 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Various documents concerning the Republic of Macedonia, Greece, and the Balkans
  - Correspondence, 2007 - 2008 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    Letters from Italy and Macedonia
  - Ekonomik Forum Magazine - Turkey, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Guides to Investing in Macedonia, 2005 - 2010 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    Includes publications from USAID and the government of the Republic of Macedonia
  - International Invitations, 2007 - 2008 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    Macedonia, Slovenia, Greece, Estonia, Italy, Israel, Belgium, Russia, Hungary, Britain, Norway, Australia, the Netherlands, Ukraine
  - International Investment - Folder 1, 1994 - 2005 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    Various foreign investment and financial guides and publications
  - International Investment - Folder 2, 2015 - 2016 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Information for Investors - Azerbaijan, Kazakhstan, Kyrgyzstan, 1994 - 1995 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Information for Investors - Russian Federation, Tajikistan, Turkmenistan, Uzbekistan, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Kazakhstan Election Observation - Folder 1, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    Expense Report, general ODIHR election observation handbook, Tashkovich's notes
  - Kazakhstan Election Observation - Folder 2, 2013 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    "Constitutional Act of the Republic of Kazakhstan on Elections in the Republic of Kazakhstan"
  - Kazakhstan Election Observation - Folder 3, 2016 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    "Information and Reference Material for observers of foreign states, international organizations and representatives of foreign mass media"
  - Kazakhstan Election Observation - Folder 4, March 2016 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    Glossary of election terminology, OSCE code of conduct, STO guide, STO protocol, interim report, photo directory, observation report forms, and additional documents
  - Kyrgyztan Constitutional Referendum, June 27, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    A photo directory of long and short-term election observers for the
  - Macedonian Informative Publications, 2006 - 2007 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Macedonia - New Government 2008, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    Includes a speech of the government mandator to announce the new government to parliament, and the CVs of the ministers program of the government.
  - Macedonian Pamphlets, Fliers, and Publications, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    In English and Macedonian
  - Macedonia - Various Articles and Informative Writings, 1999 - 2016 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    American publications about Macedonia
  - Magazines - Prince Alwaleed - Folder 1, 2006 - 2007 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Magazines - Prince Alwaleed - Folder 2, 2001 - 2007 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Programs, Pamphlets - International, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - National Aviation Strategy of the Republic of Macedonia - Final Report, June 26, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - News and Magazines - Macedonian and English Interviews with Gligor Tashkovich, 2006 - 2007 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Contains interview with Gligor Tashkovich and articles concerning him
  - Nigerian Scam Emails, 2006 -2015 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Oman - Tourism Guides, 2006 - 2007 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - ODIHR Election Observation Mission 2008: Republic of Azerbaijan - Folder 1, October 15, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Included is information about the International Election Observation Mission for the presidential election of the Republic of Azerbaijan. Guides for short-term election observers are included.
  - ODIHR Election Observation Mission 2008: Republic of Azerbaijan - Folder 2, October 15, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Contains a CD/DVD. Included is information about the International Election Observation Mission for the presidential election of the Republic of Azerbaijan. Guides for short-term election observers are included.
  - Principles and Code of Conduct for International Election Observers, October 27, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    United Nations
  - Public Enterprise for Airport Services Macedonia, 2006 - 2007 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Republic of Armenia Presidential Elections - Round 1, February 2003 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    ODIHR
  - Republic of Armenia Presidential Elections - Round 2, March 2003 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Republic of Belarus Election Observation - Folder 1, September 11, 2016 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    Observation Report Forms
  - Republic of Belarus Election Observation - Folder 2, 2003 - 2016 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    OSCE/ODIHR Election Observation Mission Short-Term Observer Guide; OSCE/ODHIR Handbook for Domestic Election Observers
  - Republic of Belarus Election Observation - Folder 3, 2005 - 2013 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    OSCE/ODIHR booklets
  - Republic of Belarus Election Observation - Folder 4, 2016 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    Glossary of election terminology, electoral code of the Republic of Belarus, regional briefing pack
  - Republic of Belarus Tourism, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Contains two greeting cards and two tourist maps
  - Sarajevo, Bosnia-Herzegovina Maps, 2008 - 2010 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Slovenia - Tourism Guides, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Society and Diplomatic Review, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    A Saudi edition saluting the United Nations.
  - UMD Voice - Macedonia, 2008 - 2010 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    United Macedonian Diaspora Publications
  - Urbanization in Africa, 2015 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - U.S.-Azerbaijan Banking and Finance Forum, May 2005 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Yugo Politics, Central and Eastern Europe - Resource Guides, 1998 - 1999 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    "Who's Who in Yugo Politics" and "Central and Eastern Europe: A Resource Guide"
  - 3rd Global Baku Forum, April 28, 2015 - April 29, 2015 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    "Building Trust in the Emerging World Order"
  - Foreign Affairs Live, ED Inspector Receipt, 2016 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Elliott School of International Affairs, 2016 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Islamic countries finance summit bag, 2017 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Almaty Management University packet, 2017 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- SERIES VIII. MISCELLANY
  - CAAAN tutorial (CD-ROM), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The Corson Symposium (DVD), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Managing the Future: A Summit on the Transformation of Business: JGSM (CD-ROM), 2004 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Seal & Serpent remarks, CAAAN Advisory Committee remarks (floppy disk), 2004 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Name tags and buttons: [Cornell] Trustees, University Council, JGSM, miscellaneous; [Business] trade shows, international telecommunications, miscellaneous; [Oil Pipelines] AMBO, Eastern Europe, Balkans, Italian symposium, Macedonia, 2001-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5-13)
  - Souvenir rocks (5), n.d. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - CACO centennial (tote bag), 2005 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - The Cornell Campaign Creating the Future (tote bag), 1992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Olde Hansa, Tallinn, Estonia: The Medieval Restaurant (paper bag, woven sack, menu, receipt), 2004 (Box 16, Folder 17-20)
  - Telecom Catalogue: 6th World Telecommunication Exibition and forum, 7/10/, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "The Architecture of Vuko Tashkovich" (Box 16)
  - C. U. hat [MU-1200] (Box 17)
  - "Big Red Live" hat [MU-1201] (Box 17)
  - Olympics t-shirts [MU-1202 - MU-1206] (Box 17)
  - Olympics visor [MU-1207] (Box 17)
  - T-shirt for Grand Prix International de Monaco [MU-2022] (Box 17)
  - T-shirt for Bidzina Ivanishvili [MU-2023] (Box 17)
  - Programs, 2006-2009 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Menus (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Misc., 2004, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Boarding passes (Box 31)
  - "Turkish Passport" program/reviews (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Travel: boarding passes, tickets, etc. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Ted Teen Conference, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Shanghai Academy of Social Sciences/Jewish Studies of Shanghai, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Boarding passes and in-flight menus (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Airline Menus (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Playbills and programs (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Second Avenue Subway grand opening map, Ammerican Embassy in Macedonia bag, luggage tags (including the Concorde) (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - NY political mailings, 2016-2017 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Second Avenue subway hat (Box 48)
- Series VIII. Audio/Visual material
  - Export potentials of Republic of Macedonia, CD-3430 (Box 47)
  - Macedonia: Your Business Destination, 2005; CD-3431 (Box 47)
  - The Protection of the Ohrid and Prespa Landscape, CD-3432 (Box 47)
  - Republic of Macedonia Ministry of Development Investment Potential, CD-3433 (Box 47)
  - Macedonia: Your Business Partner, 1997; CD-3434 (Box 47)
  - Macedonian Antiquities, 1998; CD-3435 (Box 47)
  - Helen Dunn Speech, May 2008; CD-3436 (Box 47)
  - Macedonian Export Potentials, CD-3437 (Box 47)
  - Collaborative Media Group: Film City Macedonia, CD-3438 (Box 47)
  - Macedonia Urbanism Major Prospects, Powerpoint, 2006; CD-3439 (Box 47)
  - Science and Engineering Indicators, 2002; CD-3440 (Box 47)
  - Johnson School, Cornell University, CD-3441 (Box 47)
  - Investing in Macedonia: Frequently Asked Questions, 2006; CD-3442 (Box 47)
  - Partnership and Investment Opportunities in Bulgaria, 2004; CD-3443 (Box 47)
  - Filmland Bitola a Film City in the Heart of Macedonia, DVD-2106 (Box 47)
  - Awaza Resort Pearl of Turkmenistan, DVD-2107 (Box 47)
  - To the End of the World, DVD-2108 (Box 47)